<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Problem_9_ViewPager_Fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="coldplay">Coldplay are a British rock band formed in 1996 by lead singer and
        pianist Chris Martin and lead guitarist Jonny Buckland at University College London (UCL).
        After they formed under the name Pectoralz, Guy Berryman joined the group as bassist and
        they changed their name to Starfish. Will Champion joined as drummer and backing vocalist,
        completing the lineup. Creative director and former manager Phil Harvey is often referred
        to as the fifth member by the band. The band renamed themselves "Coldplay" in 1998, before
        recording and releasing three EPs: Safety in 1998 and Brothers &amp; Sisters and The Blue
        Room in 1999. The Blue Room was their first release on a major label, after signing to
        Parlophone.</string>
    <string name="the_beatles">The Beatles were an English rock band formed in Liverpool in 1960.
        With members John Lennon, Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr,
        they became widely regarded as the foremost and most influential music band.
        Rooted in skiffle, beat and 1950s rock and roll, the Beatles later experimented with
        several musical styles, ranging from pop ballads and Indian music to psychedelia and
        hard rock, often incorporating classical elements and unconventional recording techniques
        in innovative ways. In 1963 their enormous popularity first emerged as "Beatlemania";
        as the groups music grew in sophistication, led by primary songwriters Lennon and
        McCartney, the band were integral to pop musics evolution into an art form and to
        the development of the counterculture of the 1960s.</string>
    <string name="ed_sheeran">Edward Christopher Sheeran, MBE, born 17 February 1991, is an English
        singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor.
        Sheeran was born in Halifax, West Yorkshire, and raised in Framlingham, Suffolk.
        He attended the Academy of Contemporary Music in Guildford as an undergraduate
        from the age of 18 in 2009. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended
        play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album,
        + (read as "plus"), was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts,
        reached number five in the US, and has since been certified seven-times platinum in the UK.
        The album contains the single "The A Team", which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for
        Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British
        Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. "The A Team" was nominated for Song of the
        Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</string>
</resources>
